[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐]
PAUL LEWIS: Welcome to this Supercharged TL;DW.
欢迎来到今天的Supercharged TL; DW集
I'm Paul, and last week Surma and I built a router.
我是Paul，上周我和Surma建立了一个路由器。
Let me show you what we built.
让我告诉你我们做了什么。
So you'll recognize this kind of thing
您会认识到这种事情
from progressive web apps, or in just any web app really,
在可扩展的应用程序中，
where you've got a page, and you can click on a nav,
在有页面的地方，您可以单击表面，
and it dynamically switches the section,
该部门将动态变化，
it updates the route in the address bar.
它更新地址栏中的源。
And you can click back and forth, and so on as you go.
您可以按向前和向后移动等。
Well, let's take a look at the code.
好的，让我们看一下代码。
But, no wait, before we do that, we
但是，不要等，然后再做
need to have ourselves a chat over in Theory Corner.
我们需要在“理论角”中进行对话
Oh, welcome to Theory Corner, theory in a corner,
欢迎来到理论角度，角度理论，
one of my favorite places to have theory.
思考理论的最佳场所之一。
And the router actually has to have two modes.
实际上，设备必须具有两种模式。
And a lot of people, when they make their first router,
很多人在第一次制造路由器时，
they don't realize that you need both modes.
他们没有意识到他们两者都需要。
You have an active mode, where you tell the router, actively,
您拥有主动模式，可以在其中直接对路由器说
I want to go to this URL.
您要转到此URL。
But also, you need a passive mode.
但是，您还需要间接模式。
When the URL changes, the router needs to be notified.
URL更改时，必须通知路由器。
So this is its kind of passive mode, where it's listening
这是他的间接情况，
for the popstate event.
在哪里收听popstate事件更改
what happens with the view.
显示区域会发生什么。
So the router kind of has to be the middle of your world.
因此，路由器应该在您的世界中间。
Well, of course, when you push actively,
好吧，当然，当您直接付款时，
you also need to pushState as well,
您还应该执行pushState，
and change the URL yourself.
并自行更改URL。
OK, so we've got all that set up on this side.
好吧，我们已经做好了这方面的一切。
As I say, what we do is we look at
正如我所说，我们要做的是
say the path name of the location,
网站路径名称，例如，
and then we decide, well, which view needs to come in,
然后，我们决定应该显示哪个显示区域，
which view needs to go out.
谁应该消失。
If it's the same view, then we need to just update.
如果显示区域相同，则应该对其进行更新。
And we decide all that in here, in the router.
我们将在路由器中决定所有这一切。
Welcome back to reality.
欢迎回到现实。
I love it over here.
我在这里爱他。太好了
There's code in reality.
实际上有代码。
Super duper, let's actually have a look at some code.
很好，让我们看一些代码。
First of all, let's have a look in the HTML.
首先，让我们看一下HTML。
Now, the first thing to notice is
现在，我们首先要注意的是
that we have a couple of custom elements.
我们有几个自定义元素。
Now, you don't have to use custom elements.
您不必使用自定义项目。
We just took the opportunity to give it a try.
我们只是借此机会尝试了一下。
We got sc-view here, which represents a view
这里我们有sc-view，这是一个显示区域
that we want to move between.
我们要更改它们。
The thing to notice here is there is a route attribute.
我们在这里注意到的是，这里有一个route属性。
The route attribute we're going to use
我们将使用路线功能
to decide which view should be shown, or hidden, or whatever.
确定哪个显示区域将出现，消失或类似的显示。
Further down, we also have this sc-router,
下面，我们还有这个sc-router，
and then you'll see that there's JavaScript to control both.
然后，您将看到需要控制的JavaScript。
Let's have a look in the sc-router, then, itself.
让我们看一下sc-router本身。
It, itself, extends the HTML element,
它扩展了HTMLElement
because it's going to be a custom element.
因为它将是一个自定义项目。
And you can see at the bottom, we call registerElement
您可以在下面看到我们称为registerElement
down here, and we tell it what we want.
在这里，告诉他我们想要什么。
Well, that's fine.
好吧，这很好。
And that means that we get createdCallbacks,
这意味着我们将获得createdCallbacks，
attachedCallbacks, detachedCallbacks,
attachCallbacks，detachedCallbacks，
all those kind of things.
还有这些东西。
Really, really useful, because it
非常有用，因为它允许我们拥有生命周期。
The main thing to notice is in the attachedCallback here,
最重要的是在这个attachedCallback中，
we call the addEventListener on popstate,
我们在popstate上调用addEventListener。
and we say that we've got this onChanged function.
我们说我们有这个onChanged函数。
And you will discover this onChanged function
您会发现它在此onChanged函数中
is where all the really interesting stuff happens.
所有有趣的事情都会发生的地方。
Same with the detachedCallback, we just remove it.
与detachedCallback相同，我们现在将其删除。
When you create it, we actually set up that onChanged callback,
当您创建它时，我们实际上会准备该响应
and we actually match a bunch of routes
onChanged，并且实际上匹配一组路由
you see we ask for all the views, the sc-views,
如您所见，我们正在请求所有sc视图，
and we step through each one.
他们一步步走过。
And we add a route for it, which involves
我们添加了自己的路线，其中包括
creating a regular expression from the views route
创建路线显示空间的正则表达式
and assigning it to the view, so that later on we can say,
并将其设置在显示区域中，以便我们稍后再说，
you know, which route do we have?
你知道，我们有哪条路线？
Ah, that's the view that we need to either bring in or take out.
这是我们需要显示或隐藏的显示区域。
So that's actually all the setup work.
这实际上是就职典礼的全部工作。
What we need to do is we need to have a look quickly at the go
我们应该做的是快速查看“执行”功能
function, which I mentioned over there in Theory Corner.
我在前面的理论理论中提到过。
This is the active one.
这表示活动模式。
We've got window.history.pushState,
我们有window.history.pushState，
so we're going to push the new URL.
因此，我们将推送新的URL。
And again, we call this onChanged.
同样，我们将其称为onChanged。
Well, I think we're ready to actually
好吧，我想我们已经准备好看一下onChanged，
So the onChanged itself, the first thing we do
所以这是onChanged自己，我们要做的第一件事是
is we ask for the current pathname,
我们将询问当前路径名称，
and then we step through all the routes that we have,
然后我们将浏览所有的路线
and we try and find a match.
我们尝试找到一个匹配项。
If we don't find one, well, we just leave.
如果我们什么都没找到，我们将离开。不用担心
If we do find one, that's when things get a little bit
如果找到一个，这里就是有趣的地方，
interesting, because there's three things that could happen.
因为可能发生三件事。
We either need to just bring it in,
如果没有显示区域，则需要显示它。
If there is an existing view, we need
如果有一个，我们需要
to decide whether we're just updating a view,
我们决定只更新空间，
or whether we're telling one to transition
还是叫她搬出去
out, so that we can bring our new one in.
让我们带来一个新的。
So let's deal with those one at a time.
因此，让我们一一处理。
Let's actually deal with the state
让我们处理一个已经存在currentView的情况
So there's something up on screen,
屏幕上有东西，
and it's either a match for the currentView, the new one.
它与新的currentView相同。
And if it is, we can just update it with any new information
如果是这样，我们可以简单地用任何新信息进行更新
that we might have from the URL.
我们可以从URL获得它。
If not, it's basically a replacement
如果不是，那么它实际上是currentView的替代方法。
the current one to go out.
电流出来。
And we wait on a promise here, and I'll talk about that more
我们等待这个承诺，我会在稍后解释。
Whenever the currentView has left,
每当currentView保留时，如果不存在，则可能立即发生，
we can update our reference to the currentView,
我们可以更新对currentView的引用，
and we can tell the newView to animate in.
我们可以告诉newView输入手机。
Now, you might have noticed that these in, out,
现在您可能已经注意到，这些进入和退出作业，
and update functions-- oh, there we go,
并进行更新-如果可以，我可以按两次-
and you might be thinking, well, where do those get set?
您可能在想，他们在哪里准备？
Well, remember back here, we actually
实际上，请记住这部分，
had an sc-view element, and we have an sc-view class, very
我们有sc-view元素和sc-view类，它们与sc-router状态相同。
It stands for supercharged.
这意味着它充满了电。
Kapow, branding.
卡保，使用地址。
All right, so we've got sc-router and sc-view.
好吧，我们有sc-router和sc-view。
In the sc-view, here's the in, the out, and the update.
在sc视图中，这是Login，Exit和Update。
And the main thing about the in and the out,
关于进入和退出的主要问题
particularly, is what they do is they just
特别是，他们正在做的是
simply add a class to the view.
只需在视图中添加一个类别。
And that view is going to, then, animate in.
显示屏将随后进入运动状态。
It's going to do a scale and an opacity change,
将会改变规模和透明度，
to kind of fade in or out, depending
出现和消失有些褪色，
on, well, you know, whether it's coming in or going.
根据，他是来还是去。
When that animation is finished, we fire a transitionEnd,
动画结束后，我们运行transitionEnd，
and that means we can resolve the promise.
这意味着我们可以兑现承诺。
This is an easy way for us to chain up these animations,
这是我们进行一系列动作的简便方法，
so that the in can definitely follow the out animation.
因此，入口将不可避免地跟随出口。
But you could overlap them.
但是你可以纠缠他们。
You just decide when you want to resolve the promise,
您只需决定何时要兑现承诺，
and that will cause the animation to trigger.
这将导致机芯运行。
So there you go.
就是这样
That's all that's involved in making a router.
这就是创建路由器的全部内容。
It involves making a passive and an active,
它涉及创建间接模式和直接模式，
and it also involves chaining up a few promises.
它还与一系列承诺有关。
Of course, you could make a much more advanced router
当然，您可以制造更高级的路由器，
by allowing people to load in content lazily.
通过允许人们以互斥的方式上传数据。
And if you want us to make that one in the next live stream,
如果您希望我们在下一次直播中做到这一点，
just pop a comment in below.
请在下面留下评论。
We're watching those.
我们见到她。
We're going to respond to them.
我们会回应。
And we really appreciate your feedback.
非常感谢您的意见。
So don't forget to subscribe to the channel.
因此，不要忘记订阅。
And Surma and I will be back in a few weeks
Surma和我将在几周后回来。
with another live stream.
具有新的直播流。
And I'll catch you right there.
我会在那里见你。
There is the live stream.
这是现场直播。
You should watch that if you've got a spare hour.
如果您有额外的一小时，则应收看。
Brilliant.
下方还有一个订阅按钮，
Either one will work.
两者都会起作用。
They're both good.
两者都很好。
Click one of them, though.
顺便按一下。
Good idea.
好主意